{
    "id": "3cd61a94cdc248bc966a0bdad6eebe53",
    "title": "So do I and Neither do I",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "'I'm tired.' ................................",
            "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "So do I.",
                "So am I",
                "Neither do I",
                "Neither am I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "985915f1cba64aa2a325efaa2622d820"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I was late.' '....................................'",
            "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "So do I",
                "So was I",
                "So did I",
                "Neither do I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d722081ee9c4ecabcc48c549ba6285e"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I didn't like that film.' '...............................'",
            "description": "After adding a negative idea, we can add another negative idea using the expression 'neither did I' or 'neither am I'.",
            "answers": [
                "So did I",
                "Neither did I",
                "So am I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c9c6358e4994caf9dec2936ab612d7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I didn't finish it.' '.................................'",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Neither did I",
                "So did I",
                "Neither was I"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9239571983d34961855228273b7e8f48"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I like coffee.' '................................'",
            "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. \r\n",
            "answers": [
                "So am I",
                "So do I",
                "Neither am I",
                "Neither do I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbe97f574d6f401e9740bdfe2e3b35df"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I can swim.' '.................................'",
            "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "So I can",
                "So do I",
                "So can I"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4a860ce1985448b78173e4d4b8b07b9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I'm staying for another two days.' '...................................'",
            "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "So I am",
                "So do I",
                "So am I"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "474d94de57d040a2a842ae06e9229ae5"
        },
        {
            "question": "'She has a degree in physics.' '..........................'",
            "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "So do I",
                "So have I",
                "So has I",
                "So did I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5521a9b08e2841a1b7dcda297ed9d751"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I don't have his number.' '...............................'",
            "description": "After adding a negative idea, we can add another negative idea using the expression 'neither did I' 'neither have I' or 'neither am I'.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither have I",
                "So have I",
                "Neither I have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6bd88536c3924046bb30440a72dc9851"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I found the problem very hard.' '...............................'",
            "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "So am I",
                "So do I",
                "So did I",
                "So have I"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1a5bc3d0769b4ef4a2f0f22a5e280c45"
        },
        {
            "question": "Maria can sing beautifully and ...............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so her sister can",
                "so can her sister",
                "neither can her sister"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9a494aaba6c4319952dee2db698fe08"
        },
        {
            "question": "'I had never seen so much food in my life.' '..............................'",
            "description": "After adding a negative idea, we can add another negative idea using the expression 'neither did I' or 'neither am I'.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither have I",
                "Neither had I",
                "Neither did I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "67aa9677d4e14e638eff19d99c469be6"
        }
    ]
}